// answer would be option index

import { Question } from "../types";

const questions: Question[] = [
  {
    question: "Which cricketer has scored the fastest hundred in the IPL?",
    options: ["Virat Kohli", "David Warner", "Chris Gayle", "AB de villiers"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which team has successfully defended its title in the IPL?",
    options: ["CSK", "KKR", "RCB", "MI"],
    answer: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "Who gets to wear the Purple Cap?",
    options: [
      "Cumulative - Highest Runs Scorer",
      "Cumulative - Highest Wicket Taker",
      "Man of the Match",
      "Man of the Series",
    ],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How long is a single Strategy Break during an IPL - 2 match?(in minutes)",
    options: [10, 7.5, 15, 5],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question:
      '"To be the most successful and entertaining franchise in the league" is their mission. Who are they?',
    options: ["PBKS", "RCB", "DC", "KKR"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Indian player has scored the fastest hundred in the IPL?",
    options: ["Virat Kohli", "Yusuf Pathan", "Chris Gayle", "AB de villiers"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the first cricketer to be sold at the IPL 2021 auction?",
    options: ["Aaron Finch", "Glenn Maxwell", "Steve Smith", "Moeen Ali"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who has the highest all-time batting average (having featured in a minimum of 10 matches)?",
    options: ["Chris Gayle", "MS Dhoni", "KL Rahul", "Virat Kohli"],
    answer: 2,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which batsman has scored the most number of hundreds in the IPL?",
    options: ["Virat Kohli", "David Warner", "Chris Gayle", "AB de villiers"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player has won the most number of IPL orange caps, which are awarded to the seasonâ€™s highest run-scorer?",
    options: ["Virat Kohli", "David Warner", "Chris Gayle", "AB de villiers"],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who has the highest all-time strike rate in the IPL?",
    options: ["Andre Russell", "Chris Gayle", "AB de villiers", "KL Rahul"],
    answer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many times have teams ended top of the table in the league stages before going on to win the final?",
    options: [1, 2, 3, 4],
    answer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "How many finals has Mahendra Singh Dhoni played in the IPL?",
    options: [5, 8, 3, 6],
    answer: 1,
  },
];

export default questions;
